{
    "subject": "resource/Wilhelm_H\u00f6ttl",
    "predicate": "ontology/deathPlace",
    "object": "resource/Altaussee",
    "human_readable": "Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl died in Altaussee.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9528124928474426,
            "question": "What happened to Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl in Altaussee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.872043788433075,
            "question": "Where did Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7123113870620728,
            "question": "Do you have any information about the circumstances surrounding Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6762702465057373,
            "question": "Were there any notable events associated with Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5378811359405518,
            "question": "What can we learn from Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl's death?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5349303483963013,
            "question": "Is Altaussee known for anything significant related to Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.42315202951431274,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.39040786027908325,
            "question": "How is Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl remembered today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23250702023506165,
            "question": "Are there any other historical figures connected to Altaussee?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2030658721923828,
            "question": "What is the significance of Altaussee in history?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl died in Altaussee.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6618_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any other historical figures connected to Altaussee?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6618_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How is Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl remembered today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6618_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6618_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6618_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6618_31.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6618_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6618_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6618_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6618_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6618_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6618_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6618_80.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6618_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n``` \n\n\nThe text states that Dr. Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl joined his wife in Altaussee and surrendered to American soldiers on May 8, 1945. There is no mention of him dying there. \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl joined his wife in Altaussee at the end of the war and surrendered to American army soldiers on May 8, 1945. This implies that he was still alive at that time."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}\n```\n\nThe context does not provide information about Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl's death location. While it mentions that he surrendered to American soldiers in Altaussee, May 8, 1945, there is no specific mention of where or when he died after this event."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": true,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Based on the provided context, there is no explicit statement that confirms or denies whether Dr. Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl died in Altaussee. The documents only mention that he joined his wife in Altaussee and surrendered to American army soldiers there on May 8, 1945, but do not indicate anything about his death.\n\nTherefore, the answer should be:\n\n{\"output\": \"no\"}"
        },
        "llama3.1:70b": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'no'}"
        }
    },
    "final_decision": -1,
    "actual_decision": 0,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "mistral": {
            "reason": "There is no information provided in the context to suggest that Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl died in Altaussee. On the contrary, the provided text states that he surrendered there on May 8, 1945.",
            "category": 2
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "It does not appear anywhere in the provided context information, and there is no mention of Wilhelm H\u00f6ttl's death.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}